♪Myriad delusions cut like knives♪
♪Crushing the moon in the ancient well♪
♪Lost in this life,
I never ask about tomorrow♪
♪When love runs deep,
the moonlight fades♪
♪A cursed fate,
a dream severed over lifetimes♪
=Braving the Famine with My Wife=
=Episode 15=
(My heart was gouged out.)
(How am I still alive?)
(Remember the pouch from me.)
(Keep it safe.)
It can save your life in a crisis.
(Head 3 miles east within half an hour,
or you will surely die)
Dong,
I'll listen to you.
I have walked 3 miles east.
Dong, you won't let me die here, right?
I'm so dizzy.
Didn't you already reach
the Nascent Soul stage?
Why still so weak?
(Teleportation?)
(Only True Immortals
can master such a divine skill.)
(How can he do it?)
(Could it be another ancient art?)
(I must obtain it.)
(With teleportation,)
(not even a Divine Transformation
could be my equal.)
What are you thinking?
Nothing.
Master, it was
my first time teleporting.
Want to learn?
I'll teach you.
You'd really teach me?
It's nothing.
But let's
finish our business here first.
It's Ergou!
His heart is gone.
He's still alive.
He can be saved.
His heart is gone. How can we save him?
We just give him a new heart.
Where can we find a heart?
You're putting a pig's heart in him?
You don't understand.
This pig was born
blessed by celestial fortune,
known as the Pig of Fortune.
With this heart,
Ergou will be the Son of Fortune,
shielded by the Dao.
It's done.
Reborn from ruin,
his fortune is forged.
(Ergou and I are blood brothers.)
(I'm also protected by this fortune.)
(Chaos veils the heavens.)
(I'm at the Golden Immortal stage.)
(That wretched Destined Divine Maiden
won't sense a thing.)
(The heavenly fortune has shifted.)
The heavenly fortune has shifted?
You wretched man.
You made one critical mistake.
With the shift in heavenly fortune,
the empire's fate
will change accordingly.
As long as I find the Emperor Star,
I can trace the clues and find you.
(Then, I can unleash my aura freely.)
Haven't you always wanted
to know my cultivation realm?
See for yourself.
Divine Transformation...
Void Refinement...
Body Integration?
The aura of Master Body Integration?
No, it's still climbing.
An actual Mahayana grandmaster!
Three Flowers gathered?
Five Qi converged?
This is the phenomenon
of a True Immortal!
He's a True Immortal.
My master
is a True Immortal?
All right. Don't make a fuss.
Just do your job as my maid,
and you might ascend
to the Immortal Realm one day.
Remember to take Ergou home.
Oh, my! What on earth is his origin?
I actually
thought of killing him before.
It's scary to think about it.
I should just be a good maid.
Being a maid for someone like him,
I wouldn't even trade it
to lead the Zixia Sect.
Enlightened in a pig farm...
Master is truly unmatched
throughout history.
Why stop?
Zhao Ergou, you're still alive?
Lin Weiyu, I just want
to ask you one thing.
Did you ever have
any genuine feelings for me?
Genuine feelings?
Of course, I did.
I genuinely wanted your heart.
Ergou, do you see now?
So this is the woman
you gave your heart and soul to.
You were lucky enough to escape,
yet didn't cherish it
and dared to come cause trouble.
You're truly asking for it.
For a filthy peasant like you,
giving your heart to me
is the blessing of a lifetime!
Who knew you were so tough,
not getting eaten by wild dogs,
and even had the nerve
to come here to die?
Look at yourself in the mirror.
Some backwater hick
with delusions of grandeur.
I'm the magistrate's daughter,
high above the rest.
You think you're worthy of me?
I only wanted your rare Pure Heart.
You two scoundrels
are worse than beasts!
Insolent!
Someone! Kill him!
♪With a clap of thunder,
you were cast into the mortal realm♪
♪Silk robes replaced by rags♪
♪Immortal bones buried in the dust♪
♪One thought once stirred the seas♪
♪Now, even cold porridge
is a lucky find♪
♪She was cast out of the golden hall♪
♪With only half a tattered decree♪
♪Her eyes still held a blade's edge♪
♪Saying this world
isn't worth a single moment♪
♪You handed her a bowl of coarse tea♪
♪Telling her to taste
life's bitter and sweet♪
♪So the Supreme Immortal
can fall to dust♪
♪So the Empress
can feel her heart turn cold♪
♪You watched the sunset
in a narrow alley with her♪
♪Hearing a child cry out in pain,
yet still laughing, so silly♪
♪So power is no match
for a bowl of warm porridge♪
♪So heaven can't compare
to a lamp in a broken hut♪
♪From strangers to aching hearts♪
♪From cold words to genuine care♪
♪In the humblest corners
of the mortal world♪
♪You met the most precious person♪
♪She said commoners are just numbers♪
♪You took her to see
the fields turned to scars♪
♪And the old man bent by firewood♪
♪A lifetime of bitterness
on his shoulders♪
♪For the first time,
she set aside her crown♪
♪And held an umbrella
for a drenched street vendor♪
♪You can no longer ride the clouds♪
♪But only toss and turn in the night♪
♪Still kneeling at Heaven's Gate
in your dreams♪
♪Only to wake up
with a flatbread she tossed at you♪
♪Saying, forget the gods♪
♪Just catch your breath first♪
♪So the Supreme Immortal
can fall to dust♪
♪So the Empress can turn for someone♪
♪No longer asking
who stands higher or mightier♪
♪Only asking who stands
at your heart's door now♪
♪If Heaven wants you to pass
through the street's rising smoke first♪
♪If the mortal world cannot hold you♪
♪Then carve the memories
into your palm lines♪
♪From laughter to devotion♪
♪From falling to innocence♪
♪If there's a next life, you'll still♪
♪Love a mortal once more
amidst this suffering♪